The Git Times — Monday, August 3, 2026
Reasonix Embeds DeepSeek Prefix Caching for Low-Cost Terminal AI Agents
The Go-based agent reduces token expenses via stable context handling across extended coding sessions.
AI: n8n 2.32.7 patches core import security for AI workflow integrity
Robotics: Newton Physics Engine Adds GPU-Accelerated Solver Composition for Robotics
Cyber: Wazuh tightens cluster stability and API auth in latest security platform update
Systems: TensorFlow 2.21.0 Drops Python 3.9 Support, Adds JPEG XL and Tiny Int Types
DIY: SonosESP v1.12.0 adds OTA resume and accented text support for DIY touchscreen controllers
GameDev: Nakama Adds Samsung Store Purchase Validation in v3.40.0 Release
"We are what we behold. We shape our tools and then our tools shape us."
Read today's edition — gittimes.com